Finding aid to the Alexander C. Sanger papers SSC.MS.00654
Sophia Smith Collection
- Professional Activities, 1974-2017; 5
  - PPNYC, B
    - Public Attitudes Toward Teenage Pregnancy, Sex Ed., and Birth Control, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Hams Poll, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Hams Poll: Teenage Pregnancy, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - PPFA Focus Groups - Mixed On AB, PPFA Poll Social Workers, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Commonwealth Fund: Survey of Women's Health, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - PPFA Polls, Hart etc., 1993 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Strategy Reports, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - PPNYC Vol 2, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Client Satisfaction Survey, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Harris Poll: Women's Reproductive Health, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Kaiser Poll: Contraception and Unplanned Pregnancy, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - PPNYC Attitude Study, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Gallup Poll: Women's Roles, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - PPFA Poll, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - MTV, Yale Poll: AIDS, Sex, and Health, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - PPFA Poll: Voters, 1996 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - PPNYC Poll: Activists, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - PPNYC: Lapsed Donors, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - PPNYC Focus Groups, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Minnesota Choice Attitude Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Minnesota Choice Attitude Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Kaiser Sexuality Polls, 1995-1996 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Abortion Polls, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Kaiser Sexuality Polls, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Kaiser Sexuality Report, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - PPFA Poll: Voters, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - PPFA Poll: Donors, 1998 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - PEP Research, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - PEP Research, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Population Polls, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Population Polls, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Healthcare Trends Polls, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Sense, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Public Media Center, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Abortion Polls, 1998 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Misc. Abortion Polls, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Teens Polling, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Teens Polling, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Teens Polling, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Wall Street Journal Polls, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Center for Gender Equity Poll, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Kaiser Poll: Medical Care, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - PPFA Advertisments, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Progressive Donor Poll, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Kaiser Sexuality Poll / Report, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Lake Research PPFA Poll, 2000 February (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Lake Research Strategic Findings from Poll and Focus Groups, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Population Donor Landscape Analysis, 2005 September (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - People Count Project, C
    - People Count Correspondence, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - People Count Proposal, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - People Count - Receipts, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - People Count - Legal Documents, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - People Count - Funders, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - People Count, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - People Count, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - IPPF, D
    - IPPF Literature, 2010 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Organizational Literature, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Organizational Literature, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Organizational Literature, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Organizational Literature, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Organizational Literature, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Organizational Literature, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Improving Access to Emergency Contraception in Latin America and the Caribbean, 2000 November (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Sanger correspondence, 2001 May (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation (IPPF), 2001 June 6 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - IPPF / WHR Regional Council, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2002 February (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2002 June (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2002 September (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - IPPF 50th Anniversary Symposium New Delhi, 2002 November 14-15 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting Los Angeles, 2003 February (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - IPPF / WHR Regional Council, 2003 September (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - IPPF / WHR Regional Council Assorted Associate Reports, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - IPPF / WHR Strategic Planning, 2003-2004 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2004 February (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2004 June (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - IPPF / WHR Regional Council Guatemala, 2004 June (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2004 October (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Sex and the Hemisphere Report New York, 2004 October 20 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - IPPF / WHR Benefit, 2004 October 21 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - ACS Phone Log and Diary, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Healthy Women Healthy World Gala, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - IPPF / WHR Board of Directors Meeting, 2005 February 26-27 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - IPPF / WHR: Sex and the Hemisphere Launch, 2005 March 4 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2005 August 28 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Alex IPPF San Francisco, 2005 September 29 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - IPPF / WHR Haiti Event, 2005 October 26 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2005 December 2-4 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2006 April (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - IPPF Regional Council and Board Meeting Toronto, 2006 August (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2006 November 17 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Drawing It Out Reception, 2006 December 1 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - IPPF / WHR Board Meeting, 2007 March 24-27 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - IPPF Regional Council Cartagena Colombia, 2007 September 7 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - IPPF / WHR Regional Council Cartagena Colombia, 2007 September 9 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - IPPF / WHR Annual Report, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - IPPF / WHR Dossier AUPF, 2007-2008 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - IPPF Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 March 21 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - IPPF / WHR Regional Council Meeting, 2008 August 10 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - IPPF Board Regional Council Mexico City, 2008 August 11 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - IPPF Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 December 6-8 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - IPPF / WHR Annual Report, 2008 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - IPPF Publication "Reaching Out" V 26-31, 2006-2009 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Josely Carvalho Event, 2009 December 4 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - ACS notes Tripto Colombia, 2010 October-November (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Trip to Colombia, Organizational Materials, 2010 October-November (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Pill 50th Anniversary, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Pill 50th Anniversary, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Pill 50th Anniversary, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - UNFPA Press Release, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - UNFPA Meeting Correpsondence, 2002 June (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - UNFPA Meeting, 2002 June 18-19 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - UNFPA Meeting, 2002 June (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - IPPF, 2006-2014 (Box 99)
    - IPPF/WHR - Regional Council Meeting, 2014 July 26-27 (Box 99)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting - Dominican Republic, 2014 July 22 (Box 99)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting - Dominican Republic, 2014 July 25 (Box 99)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2014 October 25-26 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Regional Director Search, 2015; 2016 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2015 March 20-22 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2015 July 17-19 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2015 November 7-8 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Financial Committee Meeting, 2015 March 17 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR Allocations Committee Meeting, 2016 March 2 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Financial Committee Meeting, 2016 March 14 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Regional Council Meeting, 2016 March 19-20 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2016 July 16-17 (Box 100)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2009 April 25-26 (Box 101)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2009 December (Box 101)
    - IPPF/WHR - Regional Council and Board Meeting, 2009 September 26-27 (Box 101)
    - IPPF/WHR, 2009-2010 (Box 101)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2010 December 11-12 (Box 101)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2011 April 2-3 (Box 101)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting and Regional Council, 2011 October 1, 3 (Box 101)
    - IPPF/WHR - 2012 Report (Box 103)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2013 July 27-28 (Box 103)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2013 November 1-3 (Box 103)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2011 October 3-4 (Box 102)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2011 (Box 102)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2012 February 25-26 (Box 102)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2012 (Box 102)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2014 April 5-6 (Box 102)
    - IPPF/WHR - Board Meeting, 2014 February 14 (Box 102)
  - Toulmin, E
    Conditions Governing Access
    The Virginia B. Toulmin Foundation materials, located in boxes 96, 97, and 98, are restricted until 2034.
    - Arts
      - ASOLO Theatre (Box 97)
      - BAM (Box 97)
      - Bronx Chapter School for Arts (Box 97)
      - Christopher and Dana Reeve Foundation (Box 97)
      - City Center (Box 97)
      - DPAA (Box 97)
      - Juilliard (Box 97)
      - League of American Orchestras (Box 97)
      - NYC Ballet (Box 97)
      - Opera America (Box 97)
      - Sarasota Orchestra (Box 97)
      - Symphony Space (Box 97)
      - Tessitura (Box 97)
      - Tighar (Box 97)
    - Toulmin, 2011 (Box 96)
    - 2012 Notes Part I (Box 96)
    - 2012 Notes Part II (Box 96)
    - Calendar Trustees MTF, March 8, 2012 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin - Dayton Meeting, March 8th, 2012 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin - Dayton Meeting, April 3, 4, 2012 (Box 96)
    - Sarasota Trip, May 7-8, 2012 (Box 96)
    - Washington, D.C., May 21, 2012 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, June 2012 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, September 2012 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin Notes, 2012 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin Foundation, Juilliard, April 2013 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, June 2013 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, September 2013 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin Notes, 2014 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, February 2014 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, June 2014 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, September 2014 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin Notes, 2015 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, February 2015 (Box 96)
    - The School of American Ballet - Female Choreographers, Spring 2015 (Box 96)
    - Preludes Opening, Playbill, June 2015 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, June 2015 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, September 2015 (Box 96)
    - My First Opera - Opera America, Fall 2015 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin Notes, 2016 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, February, 2016 (Box 96)
    - Trustee Meeting, June 2016 (Box 96)
    - Shuler/Sanger Correspondence, June 2016 (Box 96)
    - Toulmin Event, June 2016 (Box 96)
    - Origin Story by Alexander Sanger, 2017 and Memorandum, 2016 (Box 96)
    - Weekly Conference Calls, 2010-2012 (Box 98)
    - Weekly Conference Calls, 2012-2016 (Box 98)
  - Other Organizations, F
    - Mandate Reform - DNC, Alexander Sanger Staff Member, 1970 April (Box 99)
    - Century Association Art Project, 2014 (Box 99)
    - Wellesley Center for Women, 40th Anniversary, 2014 September 25th (Box 99)
    - Fred T. Sai Institute, 2014 November 24th (Box 99)
    - Population Council Pamphlets, 2014 December (Box 99)
    - Wellesley Centers for Women, Advisors, 2015 (Box 99)
    - PPNNE 50th Anniversary, 2015 August 19th (Box 99)
    - United Nations Population Award, 2016 June 23rd (Box 99)
- Memorabilia, 1991-2004; 6
  This series contains protest pins and stickers, posters and greeting cards.
  - Protest pins and stickers, 1991-2004; .5 linear feet 1 small card file box (full) (Box 90)
  - Posters, greeting cards, 1993; 2004 (Box SSC Shared 2)
- Photos, 1974-2015; 7
  This series contains photos from numerous events that Alexander Sanger attended.
  These photos are arranged in chronological order.
  - Photographs of ACS and family, undated (Box 85)
  - Photographs of ACS, undated (Box 85)
  - Photographs: Sanger Center Dedication, Oct 8, 1974 (Box 85)
  - Planned Parenthood Reception at White House, 1979 (Box 85)
  - PPNYC, 1989 (Box 85)
  - ACS with Politicians, 1990s (Box 85)
  - Benefit Dinner, May 1990 (Box 85)
  - Bleeker Street Under Construction, April 1991 (Box 85)
  - Sanger and Mayor Dinkins Playing Tennis, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 85)
  - Sanger and Mayor Dinkins Tennis Photos, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Benefit '92 Photos of ACS with Katherine Hapburn and Kathleen Turner, undated (Box 85)
  - March on Washington, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Bowling Party, Jan, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Robert McNamara Event, April 1992 (Box 85)
  - AIDS Walk, May 1992 (Box 85)
  - Planned Parenthood at the Democratic National Convention, July, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Holiday Parties and PPNYC Workshops, December, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Retreat, Dec 1992 (Box 85)
  - Clinic Defense and Staff Training, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Miscellaneous PPNYC Event Photos - Staff/Executive Board, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Miscellaneous Photos Including ACSN/Christopher Reeves and Dana Delaney, 1992 (Box 85)
  - Women's History Month, 1993 (Box 86)
  - PPNYC/Bronx Events and Parties, 1993 (Box 86)
  - ACS with New York Politicians (Giuliani/Schumet), 1994 (Box 86)
  - PPNYC Events, 1994 (Box 86)
  - Photographs Cairo Egypt - Miscellaneous Forum (including John Kerry), 1994 (Box 86)
  - Surgeon General Jocelyn Elders and Kathleen Turner, 1994 (Box 86)
  - IPPF Cruise, ACS, Jane Fonda, Senator Simpson, Pam Maraldo, etc., 1994 (Box 86)
  - Alexander Sanger and Mario Cuomo - Bill Signing, 1994 (Box 86)
  - FGM and FPA Events, 1995 (Box 86)
  - PPNYC/PPNYS/NJ Weekend, 1995 (Box 86)
  - PPNYC/PPNYS Events, 1995 (Box 86)
  - Planned Parenthood Press Conference, 1995 (Box 86)
  - Photos from Beijing, 1995 (Box 86)
  - ACS with son at Prama Anniversaries, 1995 (Box 86)
  - Sanger Family at White House, 1995 (Box 86)
  - 80th Anniversary of PPNYC Ceremony, 1996 (Box 87)
  - Staff Events, 1996 (Box 87)
  - Press Conference, 1996 (Box 87)
  - May Del Rio Party, 1996 (Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous Events, 1996 (Box 87)
  - PPNYC Photographs, March 1997 (Box 87)
  - Washington DC Photos, March 1997 (Box 87)
  - Photographs, 1997 (Box 87)
  - Shidzue Kato 100th Birthday, Tokyo, April 1997 (Box 87)
  - PPNYC and NYS Staff Photos, 1998 (Box 87)
  - MVA Press Conference, 1998 (Box 87)
  - PPNYC Holiday/December Parties, 1998 (Box 87)
  - ACS and Jeanette Watson Sanger, 1998 (Box 87)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 88)
  - Executive Staff Retreat, 1999 (Box 88)
  - Women's Leadership Forum, 1999 (Box 88)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, February 1999 (Box 88)
  - ACS speech of Women's City Club of New York, March 1999 (Box 88)
  - Information of Family Planning Luncheon, March 1999 (Box 88)
  - Bronx Parents Graduation, March 1999 (Box 88)
  - Mexico, April 1999 (Box 88)
  - Peter Purdy Party, May 1999 (Box 88)
  - Washington D.C. Event, September 1999 (Box 88)
  - Academy and Medicine Conference, November 1999 (Box 88)
  - Staff Parties, 1999 (Box 88)
  - Miscellaneous PP Events, 1999 (Box 88)
  - Photos, 2000 (Box 88)
  - FPALC Event Photos and Correspondence, February 2000 (Box 88)
  - IPPF and PP Golden Gate Events, April and June 2001 (Box 88)
  - "Sex, Lies and the Global Gay Rule", June 4, 2001 (Box 88)
  - Photographs, 2002 (Box 88)
  - Photographs, 2003 (Box 88)
  - IPPF/WHR Boarding Meeting, August 20th, 2005 (Box 88)
  - North Haven and Maine Library Reception, August 17th, 2006 (Box 88)
  - PPGGNNJ Event, June 2007 (Box 88)
  - Photographs with Various Presidents (Copies), 1981-2008 (Box 88)
  - Mailman's Party, Virginia, 2004 (Box 89)
  - Book Tours, 2004 (Box 89)
  - Lenox Hill Bookstore, February 2nd, 2004 (Box 89)
  - IPPF/WHR Regional Council Board Meeting; Guatemala, June 2004 (Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous Photos, November 3rd, 2015 (Box 99)
  - Miscellaneous Picture, Cecile Richards, June 2015 (Box 99)
- AV Material, 1990-2012; 8
  This series contains: radio interviews; historical pieces about Alexander's grandmother, Margaret Sanger; speeches; Planned Parenthood, PPNYC, and IPPF events; notes on and drafts of Beyond Choice; book tour material; photos. The different media include audio cassettes, video cassettes, compact disks, DVD's, micro audio cassettes, mini DV's, and floppy disks.
  Most of these materials are arranged chronologically within their medium.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  As a preservation measure, researchers must use digital copies of audiovisual materials in this collection. Please consult with Special Collections staff to request the creation of and access to digital copies.
  - Audio Cassettes, A
    - Fresh Air with Terry Gross - NPR - WHYY, 1993; 2 items (2 audiocassettes ) (Box 93)
    - New York Beat - WNYC, January 5, 1994; 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
    - On the Media, Host: Alex Jones - "Issues Advertising: Selling Ideas", May 1st, 1994; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 93)
    - "Planned Parenthood", August 9, 1995; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 92)
    - Margaret Sanger - The Woman Rebel - Alexander Sanger - Chautauqua Institution, 2001; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 91)
    - LBF Shaw - Alex Sanger, January 28th, 2004; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 91)
    - Alexander Sanger, February 17, 2004; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 91)
    - CBC RadioONE - Web session number 12338 - Susan Ormiston, April 23rd, 2004; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 91)
    - Family Affairs - Liz White - mix 105, undated; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 93)
  - CD's, B
    - 2. Andover Speech, February 23rd, 2007; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 3. BC Tour: Albuquerque - Massachusetts, 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 93)
    - 4. Alexander Sanger at PPHP Legacy Society Luncheons, November 7th; undated; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 5. BC Tour: Miami - Wilmington, 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 6. PPNYC Annual Reports - 20 years of paid ads, 1995-2000; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 7. PPNYC Annual Report, 1990-1994; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 8. PPNYC Annual Report, 1992; 1995; 1996; 2000; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 9. ACS. IPPF Office Documents - PPNYC/PPFA, Sanger v. Reno, ACS 1140, speeches, BC articles, 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 10. Beyond Choice - Draft + Final MS, No Date; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 11. PP North East Pennsylvania - Berks County Event, September 17, 2006; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 12. IPPF Conference - Chicago 06/LA 03/Mexico City 08, 2007; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 13. New Zealand National Radio - Alex Sanger - Feature Quest, May 18, 2010; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 14. ACS - PP Photos, 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 92)
    - 15. ACS + Politicians, Celebrities, 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 92)
    - 16. PP Photos, No Date; 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 92)
    - 17. IPPF Photos, 2005-2008; 2006; 2007; 2008; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 18. IPPF Photos, 2002 - 2009; 2004; 2007; 2008; 2009; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 19. ACS Photos, No Date; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 20. ACS - Photos - Miscellaneous, No date; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 21. Book Tour photos, 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 92)
    - 22. Planned Parenthood of Bucks County, October 23rd, 2005; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 23. Beyond Choice files, No Date; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 92)
    - 24. Document files from IPPF/WHR board meeting (by country), August 28, 2005; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 93)
    - Alexander Sanger - Colony Club, February 17th, 2004; 1 items (1 CD) (Box 93)
    - Alexander Sanger - From the IPPF Board Regional Council, Mexico City, 2008; 1 items (1 CD) (Box 93)
    - PPNYC - Public Service Announcements, undated; 1 items (1 CD) (Box 93)
    - Susan Ormiston, undated; 1 items (1 CD) (Box 93)
    - Alexander Sanger Planned Parenthood Pictures, undated; 1 items (1 CD-R) (Box 99)
    - Bookstore reading - North Haven Library (no CD, just a cover), August 9, 2001 (Box 93)
  - DVD's, C
    - 1992, 2 items (2 DVDs) (Box 91)
    - 1993, 3 items (3 DVDs) (Box 91)
    - 1994, 1 items (1 DVD ) (Box 91)
    - 1995, 3 items (3 DVDs) (Box 91)
    - 1996, 2 items (2 DVDs) (Box 91)
    - 1997, 2 items (2 DVDs) (Box 91)
    - 1998, 2 items (2 DVDs) (Box 91)
    - 1999, 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - Alexander Sanger - "External" Release - PPNYC Media (no CD, just label), 1995 (Box 93)
    - ACS - Health week - 100 years of healing - Episode #334, December 1999; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - Feminist Expo 2000 General Assembly I - Women Aloud Show #314, March 31, 2000; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - WQPT March - Alexander Sanger - Perspective #1230, March 2000; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - Planned Parenthood Golden Gate - Alexander Sanger - Raw Footage, October 17, 2000; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - SJ Roe v. Wade Event with Alex Sanger, January 27th, 2001; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - Lecture Series: Margaret Sanger -- The Woman Rebel - Alexander Sanger, July 17, 2001; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 93)
    - Planned Parenthood of Chester County Presents, October 3-4, 2001; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - Saving Women's Lives - Planned Parenthood "Keeping the Promise", November 3, 2001; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - PPNYC A Social Contract: the Abortion Provider Crisis - PP SW Florida, March 2002; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - Alex Sanger - Author of Beyond Choice - The O'Reilly Factor, January 20th, 2004; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 92)
    - Alexander Sanger, February 17, 2004; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - Your Right to Lose - A documentary for Women's Lives, April 25, 2004; 2 items (2 DVDs) (Box 91)
    - Ben Cheever TV Show AND Clemson University Communication, May 10, 2004; October 11, 2004; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - BBC Motion Gallery - Alex Sanger CS1-2, 2011; 2 items (2 DVD's) (Box 93)
    - Susan Ormiston, undated; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 91)
    - ACS PP and Beyond Choice Book Tour, undated; 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 93)
    - Alexander Sanger NY1 Clips - Early Abortion by Jeanine Aguirre and Inside City Hall segment on Subway Ads, April 20, 1998; September 30, 1997; 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 93)
    - B & W Footage - Margaret Sanger, undated; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 93)
    - Untitled DVD, undated; 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 93)
    - Happy 60th Birthday IPPF, 2012; 1 items (1 DVD-R) (Box 99)
    - Alexander Sanger Speech MCWY, undated; 1 items (1 DVD) (Box 99)
  - Micro Audio Cassettes, D
    - Alex Sanger Speeches - Forrest Church, 1991; 1 items (1 micro audiocassette) (Box 93)
    - Cairo, September 1994; 1 linear feet (1 micro audiocassette) (Box 93)
    - Cosmopolitan Club Speech, December 8, 1997; 1 items (1 micro audiocassette) (Box 93)
    - PP Six Rivers Speech, June 28th, 2000; 1 items (1 micro audiocassette) (Box 93)
    - PP Dallas, April 7th, 2000; 1 items (1 micro audiocassette) (Box 93)
    - PPNYC Speech, January 16, 2001; 1 items (1 micro audiocassette) (Box 93)
  - Mini DV's, E
    - 1992, 4 items (4 mini DVs) (Box 91)
    - 1993, 9 items (9 mini DVs) (Box 91)
    - 1994, 3 items (3 mini DVs) (Box 91)
    - 1995, 9 items (9 mini DVs) (Box 91)
    - 1996, 5 items (5 mini DVs) (Box 91)
    - 1997, 4 items (4 mini DVs) (Box 91)
    - 1998, 4 items (4 mini DVs ) (Box 91)
    - 1999, 2 items (2 mini DVs) (Box 91)
    - Margaret Sanger (B/W Footage), undated; 1 items (1 mini DV) (Box 91)
    - North Haven Library Bookstore Reading, 2001; 1 items (1 mini DV) (Box 93)
  - Video Cassettes, F
    - Planned Parenthood tapes 1-3, 1992; 3 items (3 VHS videocassettes) (Box 93)
    - Planned Parenthood tapes 1-5, 1993; 5 items (5 VHS videocassettes) (Box 93)
    - Planned Parenthood tape 1, 1994; 1 items (1 VHS videocassette) (Box 93)